https://www.partypalooza.com/privacy-policy.htm

Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Partypalooza.com. This
privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
- See what data we have about you, if any.
- Change/correct any data we have about you.
- Have us delete any data we have about you.
- Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (888) 397-2328 or via email at contact@partypalooza.com.
Categories
Crafts
Balloon Crafts
Build-A-Sticker Sets
Color-A-Plush
Color-Your-Own
Craft Kits
Paint Crafts
Holiday Seasonal
Halloween Kids Party Supplies & More!
Snowman
Patriotic
Winter
Christmas
Easter
Mardi Gras
St. Patricks Day
Summer Goody Bags
Summer Stuff
Valentine's Day
VBS-Vacation Bible School
Chanukah
New Stuff!
Party Supplies
Plates, Cups, & Napkins
Tablecovers
Decorations
Cellophane Loot Bags
Gift Bags
Gift Boxes
Tote Bags
Candy
Emojis - NEW!
Closeouts!
Cowbells
DJ & Dance Floor Giveaways
Dress Up & Costuming
Educational
Flags
Jewelry
Keychains
Lanyards
Licensed
Mustaches
Novelty Toys
Outdoor Fun
Pink Awareness!
Police
Removable Tattoos
Rubber Ducks
School Supplies
Slap Bracelets
Smiley Face
Stationery
Sunglasses
Teacher Incentives
Teachers
Wallets
Wristbands
Stickers
Use code GG2
for FREE SHIPPING, orders over $40.00! Hurry! Expires 12/31/2020.
Partypalooza Standard
Shipping Rates
Order Amount
Cost
$0.00 - $20.00
$5.99
$20.01 - $32.00
$6.99
$29.99
Orders over $400, see FAQs or call. For HI, AK & US Territories, add $6.00
Standard shipping rates above are for delivery via UPS or Post Office, at our discretion. Delivery time depends on where you live (check our FAQs for details). Shipments originate in Southern New Jersey.
Standard Shipping usually delivers within 3 business days to most of the US. Shipping to some of the Midwest, Southwest, and all of the West may require expdited shipping if you need your order in fewer than 5 business days. Faster, guaranteed delivery is available for an additional charge at checkout.
You may need to call us for next day shipping, depending on your location. Our customer service representatives are available from 9a - 5p ET. We ship only to the US and Canada.
Join Our Newsletter
Join
Copyright © 2020 Partypalooza.com Inc.. Powered by Miva
